Well, damn,
I'm feeling so existential.
Could be one as well.
Today I interviewed Robin for my MBBS with the face
and it has resulted in Robin picking out a tattoo for me.
This all came about because I asked her a question
that was 3 60 of Charli XCX
you say now my lyrics on your booby.
If someone was to get your lyric tattooed on their booby,
what lyric do you think they should get?
She was answering it and I was thinking,
I'm having a Kiki, you are such a vibe.
And you're Robin. 1
he let me in bed with you.
And 2, I'm about to ask you a favour.
It's mostly been my name. Yeah,
put my name on your body.
I would do it. It's essential.
Works too. Yeah,
I would actually do it. I'm not even joking.
Let's do it. I think of a really good one.
Okay, I'll get it done.
I pinky promise you. Oh, yeah? Yeah.
I'm dead serious. Okay, great.
I'll be there for you. It's lovely.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
Would you do that? No,
I'm dead serious. Okay, good.
After we fully wrap the shoot,
Robin stayed with us in the hotel room
and ever so kindly came up with three options.
She didn't even need to come up with one,
but she came up with 3. Dopamine.
But it feels so real to me.
I like to go out. Also,
it's quite funny cause obviously I'm Disabled,
so I don't get to go out that much,
but I like to. I would like to go out.
Like a little arrow up. And damn,
I'm feeling so substantial.
Well, damn,
Could be one as well this evening. One of them will be on
my body.
Nothing's ever gonna cut you as deep.